晚上
Good...
好  斯蒂夫伯恩特的老乡们
Evening, Stevens Point!
在此
And...
欢迎大伙来到第四频道  由格林斯坦百吉圈赞助的
Welcome to the channel four tree lighting holiday spectacular.
圣诞亮灯特备呈现
Brought to you by Greenstein's Bagels...
你们的圣诞大餐
Your schmear for Christmas cheer.
嗯嗯
Mmm!
超赞的  大家好  我是
Delicious. Hey, everybody, I'm Johnny Nimbus.
唯一一个跟你们打包票说圣诞会下雪的天气预报员
The only weatherman guaranteeing you a white Christmas.
没错  没有任何消息说今天会下雪
That's right. No other channel's predicting snow.
八频道就是这么讨厌
- Why you gotta hate, channel eight? - [Laughs]
老天啊  给我点雪吧
Cue my snow.
快点啊
- Come on. - [Applause]
哦  来了来了
Here it comes.
随时会下哦  好咧 伙计们  雪一定会下的
Any minute now. All right, it's coming, folks.
别操半个心  现在  让我们欢迎
Don't worry about it, but hey, right now, I want you to give it
家乡小甜心丽芙鲁尼
up for hometown sweetheart Liv Rooney!
和新人珍妮肯恩
And newcomer Jenny Keene.
驯鹿驾着马车停在屋顶
Up on the housetop reindeer pause.
圣诞老人悄悄下了车
Out jumps good old Santa Claus.
背着好多好多礼物从烟囱进来
Down through the chimney with lots of toys.
给小不点们准备了绚丽的惊喜
All for the little ones, Christmas joys.
好一头不知感恩的小驯鹿
How dare that ungrateful little reindeer
胆敢抢我风头  和我穿一样的可爱超萌圣诞装
come out wearing the same cutie claus outfit as me.
可恶的是她穿着胆敢比我穿着还可爱
And look cuter than me in it.
噢噢噢  谁不想
Ho ho ho, who wouldn't go?
爬上屋顶  嘀嗒嘀嗒
Up on the housetop, click click click.
去圣诞老人的烟囱探个究竟
Down through the chimney with good Saint Nick.
哎哟  不好意思  有点太淘气了
Oops. I think I just landed myself on the naughty list.
噢噢噢  谁不想
Ho ho ho, who wouldn't go?
爬上屋顶  嘀嗒嘀嗒
Up on the housetop, click click click.
去圣诞老人的烟囱探个究竟
Down through the chimney with good Saint Nick.